Choa Kim

UX Designer



UX Designer with a background of a unique blend of marketing creativity and customer service empathy. Passionate about learning real insights from user research and finding effective and creative solutions for users and businesses. A huge dog lover with a drive to create positive impacts.

Hermitage, UK choa.linzy@gmail.com https://shorturl.at/qsKZ7 123-456-789

Education

UX Design Certificate | CareerFoundry

Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

- 400+ hours intensive course for UX Designers, emphasising UX fundamentals and methodology: research methods, information architecture, personas, wireframes, prototyping user testing and analytics.
- Additionally, I learned the fundamentals of coding, including HTML, CSS, and Java.

UX/UI Design Project

Case study - A health app that fits into your daily life

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023 / CareerFoundry

- Applied the user-centred design process and a mobile first approach to design a health app that fits into people's daily lives for an easy-peasy health care.
- Defined user needs and goals through user interviews and surveys, and developed personas, customer journey maps and sitemaps.
- Designed 34 high-fidelity screens, multiple prototype iterations and a style guide through various rounds of usability and preference tests.

Experience

Customer Care Assistant | MATCHES (A Fashion Company)

Jan 2022 - Jul 2023 / London, UK

- **Collaborative:** Actively communicated with other relevant teams to address customers' challenges. Reported about 80 issues to various teams, including the product design team.
- **Creative Problem Solving:** Ideated solutions that could solve customers' issues and suggested to the relevant team to enhance customer experience.
- **Empathy and Customer Understanding:** Attentively listened to users' pain points to identify issues. Maintained a consistent Customer Service level rating of 5 out of 5.
- Time Management and Multitasking: Effectively managing multiple customer inquiries and issues, ensuring prompt responses and resolutions while maintaining a high-quality service standard.

Social Media Volunteer | British Schools Museum

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 / Hitchin, UK

- Marketing Expertise: Boosted Instagram account reach by 482%, increased engagement by 74.1%, and grew followers by 2.6% using strategic reels and stories.
- Creative: Created posts designed to attract users, incorporating current trends and SEO marketing strategies.
- **Tech-Savvy & Analytical:** Proficiency in using analytical and management tools such as Google Analytics and Instagram Analytics.

Skills

Design

UX strategy,
User flows,
Concept sketches,
Experience mapping,
Wireframes,
Prototypes,
Mockups,
Design systems

Research

User interviews, Usability testings, Persona hypothesis, Competitor analysis, Tree testing

Tools

Design

Figma, Miro, Marvel, Canva

Coding

HTML, CSS, JAVA

Product / Project Management

Slack, Notion